https://surepointtech.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Legal Management System Privacy Policy
Personal Information
At SurePoint Technologies, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit LMS without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.
If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need — for example, to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription — it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes.
Information Security and Quality
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.
Cookies
We use cookies and similar technologies to help us improve our Web sites. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. By visiting our Web site, you consent to the placement of cookies in your browser in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Business Relationships
The LMS site contains links to other Web sites. SurePoint Technologies is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
